[
  {
    "isTrue": false,
    "Question": "I live with 6 siblings and forty-leven half-siblings and cousins.",
    "Answer": "All seven of us do all live on the old man's place, but there aren't really forty-leven of us, it just feels that way."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": false,
    "Question": "I'm not afraid of anything, I'll take them all on.",
    "Answer": "I'm not even afraid of a bear one on one, but the neighbor's meany tail dogs don't fight fair, they all dog-pile on all at once."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": false,
    "Question": "I love to play ball.",
    "Answer": "Bubby, Fox, and Brie are the ball players. I'd rather go for a walk or hang out in the hammock."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": false,
    "Question": "I love smoking lady bugs.",
    "Answer": "That's sissy Tiger.  I tried one and gagged and nearly threw-up."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "I have my pilot's license.",
    "Answer": "I was the first graduate of sissy Tiger's Flight Training School."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "Bubby Mischief is my best friend.",
    "Answer": "If you want pick on him, you have to go through me first."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "The Vet has a mugshot of me on their office wall.",
    "Answer": "I was number one on the mugshot wall until this german shepard boy came along. I'm going to have to up my game."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "Murder Mittens brand 'Sea Captains Throw-up' is my favorite flavor.",
    "Answer": "There's nothing better than a little burbon flavor mixed in with your anchovies and sardines."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "I love hammocks and long walks with Gramps.",
    "Answer": "I could spend all day with Gramps or just hanging out in the hammock."
  },
  {
    "isTrue": true,
    "Question": "I love British Murder Mysteries.",
    "Answer": "I do, killing humans is the best.  But sissy Checkers is totally obsessed with them in a scary way."
  }
]
